rizap.com 2016-05-23

# piZap - free online photo editor - fun photo effects editor

## Introduction

Our Privacy Policy will inform you about how we collect and use information that you provide when using our services and that we receive when you visit our website (piZap.com, the “website”) or our Facebook App (pizap.com, http://apps.facebook.com/pizap_editor, the “Facebook app” ). We may update this policy from time to time and we recommend that you check back regularly for changes.

## What information we collect, Personally Identifiable Information

  * PiZap.com is a free online application used for making edits and adding decorations to photos. **Users may use pizap.com website without signing up or providing any personal information**. Users that create an account **must be at least 13 years old**. Users that create an account at pizap.com are not required to supply their name, address or phone number. The only required information is a username (generic), a password (encrypted), and a valid e-mail Address. **We do not make this e-mail address public. We do not share this e-mail address with any third parties.** Every effort is made to keep these e-mail addresses safe and secure. We may from time to time send emails to registered users about product updates, new features, and general announcements. Users may opt out of these emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link on every email. User's that connect via their Facebook account will have their public Facebook account name used as their piZap.com username which is displayed on their "my pizap" page and on any photo page that they create. 
  * Please be aware that when you become a registered piZap user, other users of the Services may be able to see your username or Facebook Name, in addition to any comments or submissions that you post to the Site or submit via the Services or Facebook. 
  * Please be aware that images you create with our software may be viewable by other users in our public galleries if you save them to your My piZap gallery or to Facebook. Images that you choose to download to your computer, but do not save and share on the website or Facebook App are not viewable by anyone else, are not saved on our server, and do not ever leave your local Flash Player cache.
  * We may record certain log data such as IP address, browser type, and what site you visited directly before coming to one of our sites.

## Cookies

  * Pizap uses a cookie system to keep you logged in to the site. The site login feature will not work if you do not support cookies.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to piZap.com
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to piZap users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

## Direct Notice to Parents

At piZap.com we take child protection and privacy very seriously. PiZap does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. We are here to assist parents if they feel that their child is using piZap.com inappropriately or if someone has posted a photo of your child that you would like us to remove. piZap.com is not marketed to children under the age of 13 and you must be at least 13 years of age to create a piZap account. If you are a parent and your child is using piZap.com and you wish to have any photo or account removed from the website for any reason, please contact us with a link to content or account. We will follow up with you either by e-mail or phone to verify your identity and remove the content.

## Images posted on piZap.com and Image Removal

Images posted on piZap.com are not directly linked to any personally identifiable information that has been collected by users. Users may delete or request to have deleted any image that they post to piZap.com at any time for any reason. Simply click the "DELETE" link found on your image page or contact us and include the URL (link) to the photo you wish to have removed. We will respond to the delete request within 24 hours.

## Removal of piZap account

You may request to have your piZap account removed and deleted at any time for any reason. Simply contact us and include the e-mail address associated with the account and we will send you a verification e-mail to verify that you are the owner of the account. Once the account owner is veri fed the account and all associated images will be deleted.

## Copyright of content on piZap.com

You may not use images created with content found on piZap.com for any commercial products. You may not redistribute graphics found on piZap.com except in the context of your personalized piZap images. You may place your piZap images on custom products via the link to Zazzle.com, however these products are for your personal use only and may not be incorporated into a commercial product.

## Collection of data

Please be aware that the user name you choose, and any other personally identifiable information you include in a photo may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on this web site intentionally or unintentionally.  As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address.

## Use of data and images

  * You may delete or request to have deleted any image that you have added to this website. Contact us and include the URL of the image you would like removed.
  * Images that you save to your My piZap gallery may be featured or displayed in the piZap gallery, though the chances of any single image showing up are fairly low.
  * If you view an image on this website this is offensive, vulgar, racist, pornographic, or violates a copyright, please contact us with the the link or image name.

Pizap.com takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site editor, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of the site editor, or that are not under the site editor's control. Please take time to read this site's Terms of use.

Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.

## How We Use Personal Information

  * Personal Information is used for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve the Services, features and content, (ii) to administer your use of the Services and piZap account, (iii) to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site, (iv) to better understand your needs and interests, (v) to fulfill requests you may make, (vi) to personalize your experience, (vii) to provide service announcements, and (viii) to provide you with further information we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on piZap related services. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.
  * We use information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Services and for the technical administration of the Site, to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of the Services, to better tailor both to your needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that visitors and users to and of the Services meet the criteria required to process their requests.

## Editing or deleting your account information

You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact us.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and/or by a mail message sent to the e-mail address you have provided, which is stored within your user settings.

## NO GUARANTEES

While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, the site editor is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, the site editor offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or non-disclosure of data.

## Contact information

If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact us.

## Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

PiZap cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of PiZap or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable.

## Business Transfers

PiZap may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All registered PiZap users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us. We will ask you to verify account ownership before making changes.

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to PiZap, please be advised that we transfer Personal Information to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

PiZap is owned and operated by Digital Palette LLC Based in Los Gatos, CA. Please contact us with any concerns or questions about our site. Thank You :)

1\. To enjoy additional editing tools and features, you may upgrade to a piZap PRO membership. PRO Users are subject to a monthly or an annual fee, depending on the membership plan you have chosen. You may not authorize others to use your account, and you may not assign or otherwise transfer your account to any other person or entity. You are entirely responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify piZap immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. PiZap will not be liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your account, either with or without your knowledge. However, you could be held liable for losses incurred by piZap or another party due to someone else using your account.

2\. Cancellations and Refunds Policy. We endeavor to treat our PRO customers fairly. You can easily cancel online 24 hours a day. There are no cancellation fees although there are no refunds for partial months (if on a Monthly plan) or years (if on an Annual plan).

3\. Ongoing Monthly Membership. If you have chosen a monthly term, your piZap membership will continue month-to-month unless and until you cancel your membership or we terminate it. You must cancel your membership before it renews each month in order to avoid billing of the next month's membership fees to your Payment Method. Monthly renewals occur on the "month anniversary" of your initial purchase date. We will bill the monthly membership fee to the Payment Method you provide to us during registration (or to a different Payment Method if you change your account information). Membership fees are fully earned upon payment.

4\. Ongoing Annual Membership. If you have chosen an annual (yearly) term, your piZap membership will continue year-to-year unless and until you cancel your membership or we terminate it. You must cancel your membership before it renews each year in order to avoid billing of the next year's membership fees to your Payment Method. Annual renewals occur on the "year anniversary" of your initial purchase date. We will bill the annual membership fee to the Payment Method you provide to us during registration (or to a different Payment Method if you change your account information). Membership fees are fully earned upon payment.

## Privacy Policy

**You Must be at least 13 years old to sign up for piZap.com  or the piZap Facebook App**

Welcome to the piZap Terms of Use. Please read the following important terms and conditions (“ **Terms of Use** ”) carefully. Digital Palette LLC, provides our website located at www.piZap.com (the “ **PiZap Site** ”) and our Facebook App located at www.rizap.com and apps.facebook.com/pizap_photo_editor (the " **piZap Facebook App** ").

These Terms of Use and all policies referenced in this document or elsewhere on the PiZap Site which are incorporated herein by reference govern your access to and use of the PiZap Site, the piZap Facebook App and Services. These Terms of Use are a legal agreement between you and PiZap and apply to you whether you are a PiZap Member (defined below) or a visitor just browsing the PiZap Site (collectively, “ **PiZap Users** ”). These Terms of Use limit PiZap’s liability and obligations to you, grant us certain rights and allow us to change, suspend or terminate your access to and use of the PiZap Site and Services.

YOU UNDERSTAND THAT BY USING THE PIZAP SITE, SERVICES OR YOUR ACCOUNT YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS OF USE IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR USE THE PIZAP SITE OR SERVICES. If you agree to these Terms of Use on behalf of a business, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to bind that business to these Terms of Use and your agreement to these terms will be treated as the agreement of the business. In that event, “you” and “your” will refer and apply to that business.

### Statement of Rights and Responsibilities

This Statement of Rights and Responsibilities ("Statement") derives from the piZap Principles, and governs our relationship with users and others who interact with piZap.com. By using or accessing piZap, you agree to this Statement.

  1. **Privacy**  
Your privacy is very important to us. We designed our Privacy Policy to make important disclosures about how you can use piZap to share piZap images with others and how we collect and can use your content and information.  We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy, and to use it to help make informed decisions. 
  2. **Sharing Your Content and Information**  
You own all of the content and information you post on PiZap, and you can choose whether or not to make any piZap picture public by submitting it to the public piZap gallery when you save your image. 
    1. For content that is covered by intellectual property rights, like photos and videos ("IP content"), you specifically give us the following permission: you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any IP content that you post on or in connection with PiZap ("IP License"). This IP License ends when you delete your IP content or your account.
    2. When you delete IP content, it is deleted in a manner similar to emptying the recycle bin on a computer. However, you understand that removed content may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others).
    3. When you publish a piZap image and make it “public”, it means that you are allowing everyone, including people off of PiZap.com, to view that image, and to associate it with your piZap username and/or your linked Facebook profile. 
  3. **Safety**  
We do our best to keep PiZap safe, but we cannot guarantee it. We need your help to do that, which includes the following commitments: 
    1. You will not send or otherwise post unauthorized commercial communications (such as spam) on PiZap.
    2. You will not collect users' content or information, or otherwise access PiZap, using automated means (such as harvesting bots, robots, spiders, or scrapers) without our permission.
    3. You will not solicit login information or access an account belonging to someone else.
    4. You will not bully, intimidate, or harass any user.
    5. You will not post content that: is hateful, threatening, or pornographic; incites violence; or contains nudity or graphic or gratuitous violence.
    6. You will not use PiZap to do anything unlawful, misleading, malicious, or discriminatory.
    7. You will not do anything that could disable, overburden, or impair the proper working of PiZap, such as a denial of service attack.
    8. You will not facilitate or encourage any violations of this Statement.
  4. **Registration and Account Security**  
PiZap users are NOT required to provide their real names or any other information that may be used to identify them except a valid e-mail address or a “connection” to a valid Facebook profile. In order to help maintain the security of piZap: 
    1. You will not create more than one personal profile.
    2. If we disable your account, you will not create another one without our permission.
    3. You will not use PiZap if you are under 13 without the supervision of a parent or legal guardian.
    4. You will not use PiZap if you are a convicted sex offender.
    5. If you select a username for your account we reserve the right to remove or reclaim it if we believe appropriate (such as when a trademark owner complains about a username that does not closely relate to a user's actual name).
  5. **Protecting Other People's Rights**  
We respect other people's rights, and expect you to do the same. 
    1. You will not post content or take any action on PiZap that infringes or violates someone else's rights or otherwise violates the law.
    2. We can remove any content or information you post on PiZap if we believe that it violates this Statement.
    3. If you repeatedly infringe other people's intellectual property rights, we will disable your account when appropriate.
    4. You will not use our copyrights or trademarks (including pZap, the piZap Logos), or any confusingly similar marks, without our written permission.
    5. You will not post anyone's identification documents or sensitive financial information on piZap.
